Guide to the Garrett Orr Papers, circa 1873-1994, bulk 1890s-1914, 1935-1965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Product Files Series, 1915-1994 and undated
  - Photographs subseries, 1940s-1970s and undated
    - Retail
      - Miscellaneous retail (Box 27)
      - Shopping centers (Box 27)
    - Sports and sporting goods
      - Boating equipment
        - Evinrude motors (Box 27)
        - Johnson outboard motors (Box 27)
        - Mercury outboard motors (Box 27)
      - Bowling, 1960s (Box 27)
      - Hunting and fishing (Box 27)
      - Racing, 1960s (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 27)
    - Tobacco products
      - Alpine (Box 27)
      - Benson and Hedges (Box 27)
      - Blackstone cigars (Box 27)
      - Camel (Box 27)
      - Carlton (Box 27)
      - Chesterfield (Box 27)
      - Copenhagen snuff (Box 27)
      - Duke (Box 27)
      - Half and Half (Box 27)
      - Kent (Box 27)
      - Kool (Box 27)
      - Lark (Box 28)
      - L.M. Filter King (Liggett-Myers) (Box 28)
      - Lucky Strike (Box 28)
      - Mail Pouch tobacco (Box 28)
      - Marlboro (Box 28)
      - Miyako (Box 28)
      - Murad (Box 28)
      - Muriel cigars (Box 28)
      - Old Gold (Box 28)
      - Philip Morris (Box 28)
      - Pielroja (Spanish) (Box 28)
      - Roi-Tan cigars (Box 28)
      - Salem (Box 28)
      - Saratoga (Box 28)
      - True (Box 28)
      - Viceroy (Box 28)
      - Virginia Slims (Box 28)
      - Winston (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous cigarettes, 1950s-1960s, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous tobacco products (Box 28)
    - Travel and transportation
      - Airlines
        - Allegheny (Box 28)
        - American (Box 28)
        - Continental (Box 28)
        - Delta (Box 28)
        - Eastern (Box 28)
        - Pan American (Pan Am) (Box 28)
        - Southwest (Box 28)
        - TWA (Trans-World Airlines) (Box 28)
        - Miscellaneous airlines (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Baseball parks (Box 28)
        - Circus (Box 28)
        - Communities--States and travel (Box 28)
        - Ski-doo snow transportation (Box 28)
        - Transportation, 1960s-1970s (Box 28)
        - Vacation resorts 1940s-1950s (Box 28)
- Other Photographic Materials Series, circa 1873-1970s and undated
  Photographs, negatives and slides arranged by Orr into distinct collections that stand apart from photographic items present in other series. The series is organized into two subseries--Historical Poster Images and Modern Poster Images--and therein alphabetically by product category and trade name or title.
  - Historical Poster Images Subseries, circa 1873-1914 and undated
    Large-format photographs and negatives of posters, billboards, theatre and circus signs and other advertising-related images of goods, services and entertainment events that date from the late 19th-early 20th century. Dates for individual images have been supplied where known, but not every image could be precisely dated. The images are all on modern safety film and negative stock, which suggests that the photographs might have been taken taken during the 1930s-1940s at the earliest, but a more accurate dating of the photographs themselves cannot be determined. Many of the posters bear the logos of various incarnations of the Strobridge Lithographing Company. In addition, some of the photographs have handwritten notes on the back that indicate that those images may have originated with the Chicago Historical Society, while others bear the stamp of the Outdoor Advertising Association of America Library. Anecdotal evidence further suggests that these photographs were once part of, or copies of, a historical advertisement archive maintained by OAI, but that suggestion cannot be verified. Organized into three groups--Photographs, Negatives (photographs available), and Negatives (photographs not available)--and therein alphabetically by subject category, item name, or title.
    Many images in this subseries may be in the public domain. However, it is the researcher's responsibility to comply with all copyright and trademark laws.
    For related materials see the Strobridge Lithographing Company Advertisements collection and the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives.
    - Photographs (negatives available except where noted), circa 1873-1914 and undated
      - Apparel (Box 29)
        - Kinney Brothers (Box 29)
        - M.D. Well's and Company boots and shoes (Box 29)
      - Automobiles
        - Vim trucks (Box 29)
      - Beverages
        - Alcohol and breweries, (3 folders) (Box 29)
          Includes:
          Anheuser-Busch
          Anheuser-Busch, Attack on an Emigrant Train
          Clausen Ale
          Gibson's Rip Van Winkle Whiskey, 1892
          Pleasant Valley Wine Co.
          Tosetti Brewing
          Wacker & Birk Brewing Co.
        - Soft drinks (Zesto) (Box 29)
      - Consumer goods and services
        - Appliances (stoves and furnaces) (Box 29)
          Includes Cotton Plant stoves, Thatcher furnaces.
        - Cigarettes and tobacco
          - Camel cigarettes (Box 29)
          - Chesterfield cigarettes (no negative) (Box 29)
          - Duke cigarettes (Box 29)
          - Helmar cigarettes (Box 29)
          - Murad cigarettes (Box 29)
          - Prince Albert tobacco (Box 29)
          - Tiger cigarettes (Box 29)
        - Gum (Yucatan) (Box 29)
        - Medicine (advertisement in Spanish for cod liver oil) (Box 29)
        - Soaps/Cleaning supplies (Box 29)
          Includes Magic White soap, Pearline, Sapolio.
      - Entertainment
        - Circus, (4 folders)
          - Animals (Box 29)
            Includes the Barnum Monkey Tribe, Barnum Ox, Sells Brothers' dwarf elephant and hippopotomi.
          - Barnum, Bailey and Hutchinson, (2 folders) (Box 29)
            Includes one advertisement in German (1900).
          - Circus Attractions (Box 29)
            Includes Adam Forepaugh's Circus and Menagerie; Aeriel the Flying Man (W. W. Cole); Be-Be the Flying Lady (W.C. Coup); President Garfield assassination tableaux (W.C. Coup).
        - Comedy/Musical comedy, (9 folders) (Box 29)
          Alaskan, The
          Arcadian, The, 1910
          Around the World in 80 Days
          Bad Man from Mexico, 1906
          Beautiful Adventure, 1914
          Dollar Princess, The, 1909
          Fight, The
          Gay Parisians, The, 1895
          Gretna Green, 1902
          Ham Tree, The, 1913
          Iron King, The
          Little Corporal, The, 1898
          Little Terror, The, 1909
          Marriage Market, The, 1913
          M'lle Modeste, 1904
          Mountain Climber, The, 1906
          Naughty Anthony
          Our Miss Gibbs, 1910
          Patriot, The, 1908
          Peg o' My Heart
          Rollicking Girl, The, 1905
          Runaway, The, 1911
          Saratoga
          Sergeant Bruce, 1905
          Such a Little Queen, 1905
          Sunshine Girl, The
          Toreador, The, 1903
        - Magic
          - Blackstone (Box 29)
        - Minstrel shows
          - Primrose and Dockstader's Minstrels, 1913 and undated (Box 29)
          - Mammoth Minstrels (Box 29)
          - Mastodon Minstrels, 1878 (Box 29)
        - Musical/Operetta, (3 folders) (Box 29)
          Babes in Toyland, 1904
          Chieftain, The, 1895
          Fluffy Ruffles
          Gypsy, The, 1912
          Little Cherub, The
          Quaker Girl, The
          Storks, The, 1892
        - Opera (no negatives available), (4 folders)
          - Actors
            - Drew, John (Box 29)
            - Jefferson, Joseph (Box 29)
            - Knight, Geo S. (Box 29)
            - Lauder, Sir Harry (Box 29)
            - Rowe, George F., 1875 (Box 29)
          - Actresses
            - Bernhardt, Sarah, 1905 (Box 29)
            - Mitchell, Maggie (Box 29)
            - Russell, Lillian (Box 29)
          - Productions (Box 29)
            Fleur de Lis, 1895
            Othello
            Spider & Fly
        - Plays, (23 folders) (Box 29)
          Arsne Lupin, 1909
          The Auctioneer, 1901
          Barbara Frietchie, The Frederick Girl, 1900
          Bedford's Hope, 1905
          Bird of Paradise, 1913
          Black Crook
          Bonnie Scotland, 1895
          Butterfly on the Wheel, 1912
          Chantecler, 1911
          Child of the Regiment, 1906
          Curse of Drink, The, 1904
          Damaged Goods
          D'Arcy of the Guards
          Darling of the Gods, The, 1903
          Dawn of a To-Morrow, The, 1910 (written by Frances Hodgson Burnett, author of A Little Princess and A Secret Garden)
          Easiest Way, The, 1907
          Factory Girl, The, 1903
          Fighting Hope, The, 1908
          Fool of Fortune, 1896
          For His Brother's Crime, 1903
          Girl of the Golden West, The, 1906
          Harvest Moon, The, 1909
          Harvester, The, 1904
          He Fell in Love with His Wife, 1912
          Heart of the Klondike, 1897
          Heart of Maryland, The, 1904
          Hearts are Trumps, 1900
          Hon. John Grigsby, 1901
          John Mishler, One of the Finest
          Lady Rose's Daughter, 1902
          Last Stroke, A Story of Cuba's Fight for Freedom, 1900
          Lion and the Mouse, The, 1904
          Little Minister, The, 1897 (written by J.M. Barrie, author of Peter Pan)
          Lost Paradise, The (written by David Belasco and Henry DeMille, Cecil B. DeMille's father)
          Lottie the Poor Sales Lady, or, Death Before Dishonor, 1907
          Maister of Woodbarrow, The
          Mice and Men, 1903
          Mile a Minute
          Music Master, The, 1904
          Night's Frolic
          Ninety and Nine, The
          Old Curiosity Shop, The, 1909
          Parted on Her Bridal Tour, 1907
          Peter Pan, 1907
          Prince of India, The, 1905
          Queen of the White Slaves, 1903
          Rainbow, The, 1913
          Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm, 1911
          Rebel, The, 1900
          Red Mill, The, 1908
          Rose of the Rancho, The, 1907
          Runnymede, 1895
          Sidewalks of New York, The, 1895
          Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs
          Speckled Band, The, 1910
          Spoilers, The, 1907
          Third Degree, The, 1898
          Tree of Knowledege, The, 1898
          Trelawny of the Wells, 1898
          Trip to Chinatown
          Uncle Tom's Cabin (produced by Jay Rial and featuring genuine trained bloodhounds)
          Virginius
          Warrens of Virginia, The, 1908 (written by William C. DeMille, brother of Cecil B. DeMille)
          Way Down East, 1898
          White Slave, The
          Woman, The, 1911 (written by William C. DeMille, brother of Cecil B. DeMille)
        - Variety/Tour shows/Sporting events
          - Anna Held's All Star Varit Jubilee, 1913 (Box 29)
          - Annual Tour of Minnie Dupree (Box 29)
          - B.B. Floyd's Rompo Frolique (Box 29)
          - Corbett v. Fitzsimmons Boxing Championship of the World re-match, 1897 (Box 29)
          - The Ferris Wheel at the World's Columbian Exposition, 1893 (Box 29)
          - World's Fair, Grand Columbian Carnival, 1893 (Box 29)
      - Farm equipment (McCormick Harvesting Machine Co.)
        - Battle of Gettysburg advertisement, circa 1885 (Box 29)
        - Battle of Shiloh advertisement, 1885 (Box 29)
      - Hotels
        - Palmer House, Chicago, circa 1873 (Box 29)
        - Grand Pacific Hotel, Chicago, 1874 (Box 29)
      - Political
        - Reciprocal trade (U.S.-Canada)
          - Market of 60 Millions, 1891 (Box 29)
          - Yankee Pedlar in Hard Luck, 1896 (Box 29)
      - Public service
        - Conserve Coal (Box 29)
        - Field Hospitals Overseas, Lest We Forget (Box 29)
      - Travel and transportation
        - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1877 (Box 29)
        - Crown gasoline (Box 29)
        - Wabash Route (Box 29)
    - Negatives (photographs available), circa 1873-1914 and undated
      Negatives correspond to the historical poster photographs listed above.
      - Apparel (Box 30)
        - Kinney Brothers (Box 30)
        - M.D. Well's and Company boots and shoes (Box 30)
      - Automobiles
        - Vim trucks (Box 30)
      - Beverages
        - Alcohol and breweries, (3 folders) (Box 30)
        - Soft drinks (Zesto) (Box 30)
      - Consumer goods and services
        - Appliances (includes stoves and furnaces) (Box 30)
        - Cigarettes and tobacco
          - Camel cigarettes (Box 30)
          - Duke cigarettes (Box 30)
          - Helmar cigarettes (Box 30)
          - Murad cigarettes (Box 30)
          - Prince Albert tobacco (Box 30)
          - Tiger cigarettes (Box 30)
        - Gum (Yucatan) (Box 30)
        - Medicine (advertisement in Spanish for cod liver oil) (Box 30)
        - Soaps/Cleaning supplies (Box 30)
      - Entertainment
        - Circus, (4 folders)
          - Animals (Box 30)
          - Barnum, Bailey and Hutchinson, (2 folders) (Box 30)
            Includes one advertisement in German.
          - Circus attractions (Box 30)
        - Comedy/Musical comedy, (9 folders) (Box 30)
        - Magic
          - Blackstone (Box 30)
        - Minstrel Shows
          - Mammoth Minstrels (Box 30)
          - Mastodon Minstrels (Box 30)
          - Primrose and Dockstader's Minstrels (Box 30)
        - Musical/Opera/Operetta, (3 folders) (Box 30)
        - Plays (Box 30)
        - Variety/Tour shows/Sporting events
          - Anna Held's All Star Varit Jubilee (Box 30)
          - Annual Tour of Minnie Dupree (Box 30)
          - B.B. Floyd's Rompo Frolique (Box 30)
          - Corbett v. Fitzsimmons Boxing Championship of the World re-match (Box 30)
          - The Ferris Wheel at the World's Columbian Exposition (Box 30)
          - World's Fair, Grand Columbian Carnival (Box 30)
      - Farm Equipment (McCormick Harvesting Machine Co.)
        - Battle of Gettysburg advertisement, circa 1885 (Box 30)
        - Battle of Shiloh advertisement, 1885 (Box 30)
      - Hotels
        - Palmer House, Chicago (Box 30)
        - Grand Pacific Hotel, Chicago (Box 30)
      - Political
        - Reciprocal Trade--Canadian (Box 30)
      - Travel and Transportation
        - Chicago and Northwestern Railway (Box 30)
        - Crown Gasoline (Box 30)
        - Wabash Route (Box 30)
      - Public Service
        - Conserve Coal (Box 30)
        - Field Hospitals (Box 30)
    - Negatives (photographs NOT available), undated
      - Automobiles (Box 30)
        Includes Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ford, Moon Motor cars, Pontiac.
      - Automotive miscellaneous (Box 30)
        Includes Honda motorcycles, United States Tires.
      - Beverages
        - Coca-Cola (Box 30)
        - Pepsi, (3 folders) (Box 30)
        - Various (Box 30)
          Includes Chase and Sanborn, Folger's Coffee, Orange Squeeze soda.
      - Candy (Box 30)
        Includes Honey Scotch Candies, Wrigley's, Adams California Fruit Gum.
      - Foods (Box 30)
        Includes Campbell's Soup, Meadow Gold Butter, Borden's Milk.
      - Public Service (Box 30)
      - Retail
        - Hastings Department Stores, (3 folders) (Box 30)
        - Kuppenheimer Clothing (Box 30)
        - Robinson's Department Store (Box 30)
      - Tobacco-cigarettes (Box 30)
        Includes Lucky Strike, Kool and Camel.
      - Tobacco-miscellaneous (Box 30)
        Includes Robert Burns cigars, Prince Albert tobacco.
  - Modern Poster Images Subseries, circa 1960-1970s
    Photographs, negatives and slides depicting billboard advertisements, location shots, and images of bill-posting in progress, dating primarily from the 1960s-1970s. The photographs, negatives and slides were originally kept by Orr, but it is not clear whether Orr was directly involved in the images' production, or whether they were collected for other purposes. Also, there is no readily determined relation among the photographs, negatives and slides contained herein. While there may be some duplication of images found elsewhere in the collection, there is no evidence to link these photographs with other photgraphic or negative materials found in the papers.
    - Photographs (negatives NOT available), circa 1960s-1970s
      - Outdoor advertising designs notebooks 1-4, (10 folders) (Box 31)
      - Posed character studies and miscellaneous photographs, (3 folders) (Box 31)
    - Negatives (photographs NOT available), undated
      Negatives bear no apparent relation to the modern poster photographs in the subseries above. Arranged by type and therein alphabetically.
      - 35mm Film strips
        - A-G (Box 32)
        - G-Minute Maid (Box 32)
        - Minute Maid-Worthington Air Conditioning (Box 32)
      - Loose negatives
        - Ford, (8 strips) (Box 32)
        - Location shots, presentations, samples (Box 32)
        - Pepsi, (4 strips) (Box 32)
        - Supermarket Presentation Charts (Box 32)
        - Miscellaneous, (11 strips) (Box 32)
    - Slides, circa 1960s-1970s
      Contains slides of billboard advertisements, location shots, and images of bill-posting in progress, originally housed in binders. There may be some duplication of images found elsewhere in the collection, but there is no evidence to link the slides with other photgraphic or negative materials found in the collection.
      - Notebook 1 (Box 33)
      - Notebook 2, (Sleeves 1-8 of 24) (Box 33)
      - Notebook 2 (continued), (Sleeves 9-24 of 24) (Box 34)
      - Notebook 3 (Box 34)
      - Various loose slides (Box 34)
- Sketches Series, 1930s-1960s and undated
  Sketches, drawings and paintings done by Orr at various stages in his career. The series is arranged into two subseries: Billboard and Poster Designs and Non-Advertising Sketches. The Billboard and Poster Designs subseries contains around 400 sketches of billboard designs, organized by product type and brand name. The Non-Advertising Sketches category contains sketches and drawings, along with a few small paintings, that provide a glimpse into the range of Orr's interests as an artist as well as revealing something of his artistic method. There are numerous studies of male and female forms and faces, caricatures, still life drawings, along with street scenes and backdrop art for outdoor advertising. Also included is a copy of a Vanity Fair cover which Orr did in 1935, and several illustrations for the book jackets of popular novels. Arranged alphabetically. Oversized materials have been removed to Oversize Folders 2-9.
  - Billboard and Poster Designs Subseries, 1940s-1962 and undated
    [See also Oversize Folders 2-6.]
    - Advertising self promotions (Box 35)
      - Advertising Helped (Box 35)
      - Advertising Helps
        - Beaver (Box 35)
        - Couple (Box 35)
        - Mother Hubbard (Box 35)
        - Ruler (Box 35)
        - Shopper (Box 35)
        - Sign Post (Box 35)
      - If It Will Work in Outdoor (Box 35)
      - It's Advertised Outdoors (Box 35)
      - OAI (Outdoor Advertising, Inc.) logo (Box 35)
      - Outdoor Advertising Sells (Box 35)
      - Posters Sell (Box 35)
      - Progress with Posters (Box 35)
      - Welcome to the 68th OAAA Convention (Box 35)
    - Agricultural
      - Arcadian (Box 35)
      - Westinghouse, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Automotive
      - Chevrolet (Box 35)
      - Chrysler--Mopar (Box 35)
      - Dodge, (4 folders) (Box 35)
      - Fiat, (5 folders) (Box 35)
      - Ford, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - General Motors, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Mazda, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Plymouth, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - VIM (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Automotive accessories
      - WIX, (6 folders) (Box 35)
    - Automotive--Tires
      - General, (5 folders) (Box 35)
      - General Jet-Air, (11 folders) (Box 35)
      - Lee, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - U.S. Tires, (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Banks
      - Bowery Savings Bank (Box 35)
      - Dekalb City Federal (Box 35)
      - Florida National Bank (Box 35)
    - Beer
      - Falstaff, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - Feigenspan, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Jax, (4 folders) (Box 35)
      - Krueger's (Box 35)
      - Schmidt's, (7 folders) (Box 35)
    - [Billboard proofs: removed to Oversize Materials, Oversize Folder 2.] (Box 35)
    - Businesses
      - J.M. Monk Building Company (Box 35)
    - Drugs
      - Forhan's, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Geritol (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Food and beverages
      - American Dairy Association (ADA), (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. (A&P) (Box 35)
      - Baker's Cocoa, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Best Foods, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Betty Crocker (Box 35)
      - Blue Plate (Box 35)
      - Cliquot Club (Box 35)
      - Coca-Cola (Box 35)
      - Del-Monte, (8 folders) (Box 35)
      - Hardee's (Box 35)
      - Heinz, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Hellmann's (Box 35)
      - Luck's (Box 35)
      - Mars, (4 folders) (Box 35)
      - Nabisco, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - National Confectioners Association (Box 35)
      - Nescafe, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - Sunshine, (8 folders) (Box 35)
      - Swift's (Box 35)
      - Tetley's, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Yuban (Box 35)
    - Fuel-Automotive
      - Atlantic Motor Oil (Box 35)
      - Enco, (18 folders) (Box 35)
        Includes a note written by Orr in the first folder.
      - Fina (Box 35)
      - Gulf (Box 35)
      - Kool Motor, (5 folders) (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
      - Pyro, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Shell
        - Black Cat campaign, (8 folders) (Box 35)
        - Love campaign, (12 folders) (Box 35)
        - Research campaign, (20 folders) (Box 35)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
      - Sinclair, (13 folders) (Box 35)
      - Sunoco, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Fuel-Home
      - Gas, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Semet Solvay coke (Box 35)
    - Household and personal products
      - Gillette, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Glory-B wax (Box 35)
    - Insurance
      - MetLife, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Liquor
      - ACF Gin (Box 35)
      - Bellow's, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Black and White, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Carstair's (Box 35)
      - Dewar's (Box 35)
      - Haig and Haig, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - MacNaughton (Box 35)
      - Old Colony (Box 35)
      - Old Crow, (10 folders) (Box 35)
      - Seagram's, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - Smirnoff, (5 folders) (Box 35)
    - Media
      - Printed material
        - Cover design for 100 Best Posters, 1936 (Box 35)
        - Cover designs for Interpace annual report, (5 folders) (Box 35)
      - Records
        - Decca, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - Television
        - Dragnet, (2 folders) (Box 35)
        - Eddie Fisher Show (Box 35)
    - Photographic (Box 36)
      - Polaroid Polacolor film, (6 folders) (Box 36)
    - [Poster designs: removed to Oversize Materials, Oversize Folder 3-6.] (Box 36)
    - Public service messages
      - Export $$$ Helps Pay U.S. Money (Box 36)
      - National Recovery, (3 folders) (Box 36)
      - U.S. Defense Bonds, (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - World War II-Combat (Box 36)
    - Recreation
      - Copacabana, (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - Cruis-Along boats (Box 36)
    - Tobacco
      - Blackstone (Box 36)
      - Chesterfield, (8 folders) (Box 36)
      - Dutch Masters (Box 36)
      - Granger, (5 folders) (Box 36)
      - L&M
        - Live Modern, (8 folders) (Box 36)
        - Lots More, (3 folders) (Box 36)
        - Miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 36)
      - Lucky Strike, (4 folders) (Box 36)
      - Salem (Box 36)
      - Vintage White Owl, (3 folders) (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous images
      - 1 Unit (Box 36)
      - 2 Ideas (Box 36)
      - 3 Elements (Box 36)
      - "America" train, (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - Demonstration (Box 36)
      - Even the 'Rocks' Taste Better (Box 36)
      - Excite (Box 36)